ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Jacobson, Charles with Rosenberg and Sol Polakoff, portrait shot wearing delegates badges (item no.211) (Box 9, Folder 211)
- Price, George Dr. portrait (item no.212) (Box 9, Folder 212)
- Katofsky portrait (item no.213) (Box 9, Folder 213)
- Heller, Jacob portrait (item no.214) (Box 9, Folder 214)
- Heller, Jacob candid presenting check to army officer (item no.215) (Box 9, Folder 215)
- Heller, Jacob portrait at desk (item no.216) (Box 9, Folder 216)
- Heller, Jacob speaking at meeting (item no.217) (Box 9, Folder 217)
- The Lyceum (item no.218) (Box 9, Folder 218)
- Ashbes Funeral (item no.219) (Box 9, Folder 219)
- Heller, Jacob candid under flower wreath labeled Success, shaking hands with another man (item no.220) (Box 9, Folder 220)
- Shore, Samuel portrait (item no.221) (Box 9, Folder 221)
- Hillman, Sidney speaking (item no.222) (Box 9, Folder 222)
- Hillman, Sidney candid, seated at table (item no.223) (Box 9, Folder 223)
- Hillman, Sidney candid, standing hand out, in conversation (item no.224) (Box 9, Folder 224)
- Dubinsky and Hillman seated conversing (item no.225) (Box 9, Folder 225)
- Hillman, Sidney seated at table at convention, laughing, Dubinsky wearing delegates badge leaning over him (item no.226) (Box 9, Folder 226)
- Hillman, Sidney with Dubinsky and Luigi Antonini at railroad station (item no.227) (Box 9, Folder 227)
- Hillman, Sidney seated in front of microphone speaking (item no.228) (Box 9, Folder 228)
- Demonstration against Communists in front of Union Headquarters at 3 West 16th Street, Dec. 13, 1926 (item no.229) (Box 9, Folder 229)
  December 13th
- Part of 600 pickets picked up 9/13/1926. (P) (item no.230) (Box 9, Folder 230)
  December 13th (P)
- Strike pickets receive pamphlets from strike committee, Bryant Hall, 2/4/1930. (P) (item no.231) (Box 9, Folder 231)
  February 4th (P)
- Some of 27 pickets outside West Side Court after their release 9/29/1930. (P) (item no.232) (Box 9, Folder 232)
  September 29th (P)
- Pickets marching down 7th Avenue, 2/16/1932 (P) (item no.234) (Box 9, Folder 233)
  Febraury 16th (P)
- Clash between rival factions, arraigned in Jefferson Market court (item no.235), 1927 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  March 7th
- Trouble outside Madison Square Garden between rival factions (item no.236), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  December 18th
- Union Square Meeting (item no.237), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  October 16th
- Just before battle, right wingers arrive to take over Union headquarters at 130 E.25th Street, June 24, 1927 (item no.238) (Box 9, Folder 237)
  June 24th
- Police clear out International Ladies Garment Headquarters, 3 W. 16th Street after street rumpus, Dec.14, 1926 (item no.239) (Box 9, Folder 238)
  December 14th
- Madison Square Garden, Mass Meeting, Feb. 6, 1936 (item no.240) (Box 9, Folder 239)
  February 6th
- Madison Square Garden - NRA Victory Meeting, Oct. 4, 1933 (item no.241) (Box 9, Folder 240)
  October 4th
- Unemployed in front of Bryant Hall, Jan. 28, 1931 (item no.242) (Box 9, Folder 241)
  January 28th
- Riot, June 23, 1927 (item no.243) (Box 9, Folder 242)
  June 23rd
- West 37th Street, Start of Strike, 7/1/1926. (P) (item no.244) (Box 9, Folder 243)
  July 1st (P)
- Vote to end strike, 2/21/1923 (P) (item no.245) (Box 9, Folder 244)
  February 21st (P)
- Crowd on steps of Local 25 Headquarters, June 16th, 1925 (item no.246) (Box 9, Folder 245)
  June 16th
- Cloakmakers support Steel Strike, pose in front of Forward offices holding up copies of Forward telling of strike (item no.247) (Box 9, Folder 246)
- Old Unity House, Forest Park, Pa. social and dining hall (item no.248) (Box 9, Folder 247)
- Rare view of International Ladies Garment members pouring out of Union Meeting at Old Huntington Hall, 1915 or 1916 (item no.249), 1915/6 (Box 9, Folder 248)
- Local 22, First Administration, 1921 (item no.250) (Box 9, Folder 249)
- Local 25 Executive officers, 1915 (item no.251) (Box 9, Folder 250)
- Morris Sigman speaks from window at 3 West 16th Street during factional strife in International Ladies Garment (item no.252), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 251)
- Loyal Members in front of 3 West 16th Street in support of Administration (item no.253), 1926 (Box 9, Folder 252)
- Chicago Joint Board (item no.254) (Box 9, Folder 253)
- International Ladies Garment Library at Los Angeles Sanitarium, Interior and exterior (item no.255) (Box 9, Folder 254)
- Interior of room International Ladies Garment Hospital Building at Los Angeles Sanitarium (item no.256) (Box 9, Folder 255)
- Exterior view of International Ladies Garment buildings at Los Angles Sanitarium (item no.257) (Box 9, Folder 256)
- Union officials visiting Los Angeles Sanitarium, Antonini, Zimmerman and others on grounds of Sanitarium (item no.258) (Box 9, Folder 257)
- Fall River Health Center Story (item no.259) (Box 9, Folder 258)
- International House Tel Aviv, Israel, Building and Activities (item no.260) (Box 10, Folder 1)
- International Ladies Garment School Building in Italy, Franklin D. Roosevelt Institution, Palermo Building and Activities (item no.1) (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Gompers, Samuel calls on Senator Bob LaFollette at his hotel in New York left to right: Senator LaFollette, Gompers and Bob LaFollette Jr., 1924 (item no.2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Hammer made by students at International House, Haifa, Isreal; presented by students to David Dubinsky (ORT gift) (P) (item no.3) (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Crone, Harry with Louis Stark (P) (item no.4) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- KFMV Transmitter Building, Mt. Wilson, California (item no.5) (Box 10, Folder 6)
- KFMV Studios-6540 Sunset Blvd. On Radio Row, Los Angeles, CA, Interior and Exterior (item no.6) (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Cloak Agreement signed 7/16/29 (item no.7), 1929 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  July 16, 1929. Seated: Walker and I. Grossman (President of Industrial Council) standing: Morris Hoft (President Merchants Association), J. Schwartz (President American Association), R. Ingersoll (Impartial Chairman), Leiutenant Govenor Lehman and Schlesi
- Price, George Dr. and Harry Wander at dinner (item no.8) (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Ashbes working at table, scratching head (item no.9) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Polletti, Chas and family (portraits), 4/5/55 (item no.10), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  April 5th
- Held, Adolph and Meyer Perlstein (profiles) Held seated at desk, Perlstein standing arms crossed (item no.11) (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Nye, Senator profile (item no.12) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Linderman, Edward Dr. seated, Julius Hochman speaking (item no.13) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Feinberg, Israel and Walter Reuther shake hands candid (item no.14) (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Dubinsky presents check for Holland Labor Unions to represenatatives from Holland at dinner (item no.15) (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Dubinsky, Mrs. Roosevelt and Dr. Childs at dinner (item no.16) (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Dubinsky, Mrs. Roosevelt and Mabel Durham (item no.17) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Montana, Vanni broadcasting over WEVD, 1947 (item no.18) (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Dworkin, Louis speaking (item no.19) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Hochman speaking at luncheon (item no.20) (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Lehman, Sam Shore, and Mitchell Sneider at dinner (item no.21) (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Lehman and Mrs. Roosevelt (profiles) shaking hands (item no.22) (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Dubinsky and Holland Trade Unionists seated on couch conferring (item no.23) (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Nagler, Isidore speaking at Hotel Pennsylvania (item no.24) (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Lehman, Senator Mead, and Mrs. Roosevelt wearing leis, being serenaded by Hawaiian guitarists (item no.25) (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Dubinsky at Unity House hanging from high bar by feet (item no.26) (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Danish, Max and Reiner seated on couch (item no.27) (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Price, George Dr. and Mrs. Price and Pauline Newman seated at dinner (item no.28) (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Dubinsky, Hannah Haskell, and Umhey at desk in Dubinskys office during filming of March of Time movie, cameraman at work in foreground (item no.29) (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Dubinsky, Mrs. Dubinsky and Joe Tuvim seated at dinner (item no.30) (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Local 62 Executive Board, circa 1914 (item no.31) (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Seven freed officials visit Abraham Cahan at the Forward Singer Weidinger, Holtzer, Stupniker, Wolfe, Metz, M. Sigman, Abraham Cahan, Schlesinger (item no.32) (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Gompers, Samuel portrait (item no.33) (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Barker, D. with Dr. Childs, George Counts, Dubinsky, Mrs. Roosevelt, HH Lehman (item no.34) (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Buildings in China, Buildings and Activities (item no.35) (Box 10, Folder 36)
- WVUN, Chattanooga, Tennesse 1) Transmitter and Studio Building;2) WVUN Display Booth at Industrial Show (P) (item no.36) (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Chicago Convention, 1920-Local 10 Delegates l to r: Sidney Rothenberg, Meyer Sharp, Samuel Perlmutter, Davis, Harry Berlin (P) (item no.37) (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Convention-1920-Chicago-Local 10 DelegatesMeyer Sharp, Max Gorenstein, Harry Berlin, John Ryan, Louis Lipshitz, Sam Shenker, Samuel Perlmutter, Sidney Rothenberg and David Dubinsky (P) (item no.38) (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Cartoons from old issues of Justice (item no.39) (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Girl working at special machine, adjusting knob at top (P) (item no.40) (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Interior of first aid station, doctor and nurse treating girls shoulder (item no.41) (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Lobby of A Building, people sitting around (P) (item no.42) (Box 10, Folder 43)
- A Building, many people on lawn (P) (item no.43) (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Old Justice cartoon showing huge fist rising out of throng of people (item no.44) (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Porch of the Administration Building (P) (item no.45) (Box 10, Folder 46)
- St. Louis Joint Board (item no.46) (Box 10, Folder 47)
- WVUN Radio Car, John Martin standing next to truck (P) (item no.47) (Box 10, Folder 48)
- New York Health Center, 1950 (item no.48) (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Lieberman portrait, 1915 (P) (item no.49) (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Group at Unity House, Overlook MTNY Unity House 1918, including Baroff and Horowitz (item no.50) (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Dubinsky, Franklin D. Roosevelt Jr. and William Green, 4/12/49 (N.Y.) (item no.51), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  April 12th
- Gingold, David, William Ross and Jack Halpern portraits, 1951 (item no.52) (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Interior Administration building, lounge-Diega Rivera Murals (P) (item no.53) (Box 10, Folder 54)
- St. Lawrence Textile Strike, 1912. (P) (item no.54) (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Textile shop women at work, 1912 (item no.55) (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Textile shop, woman tending loom, 1912, Missing (item no.56) (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Woman at work in factory making flowers (2 negs), Missing (item no.57) (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Women at work in shop making hats (item no.58) (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Morris Sigman Home in France,Village of Maisons-Laffitte (20 miles outside of Paris) ACME-Buildings and Activities (item no.59) (Box 10, Folder 60)
  (P and 11 negatives)
- Carlo Tresca Institute, Montecompatri (Rome) Italy, 9 negs. ACME Building and Activities (item no.60) (Box 10, Folder 61)
  (9 negatives)
- ORT Vocational Training Centre of P Montreuill, Paris, France, 11negs. ACME Building and Activities (item no.61) (Box 10, Folder 62)
  (11 negatives)
- S. Mendelsohn Home for Children, Local 117, in France 10 negs. ACME-Building and Activities (item no.62) (Box 10, Folder 63)
  (10 negatives)
- Old Cartoon- International Ladies Garment View of CIO - AFL feud, Fall River Herald News (item no.63) (Box 10, Folder 64)
- N.Y. World Telegram Carton on the Nature of a Contract (item no.64) (Box 10, Folder 65)
- A Fitzpatrick cartoon in the St. Louis Post Dispatch upon opposition of the Nell Donnelly Garment Co. and former U.S. Senator James Reed to Modern Collective Bargaining (item no.65) (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Cartoon on Sweat shops ---Nice Buildings But---Sweatshops just the Same (item no.66) (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Dubinsky and Dr. George Price conversing (P) (item no.67) (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Dubinsky at Barbizon Corporation with other union officials, operating outfitting machine, etc. (11 negatives) (item no.68) (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Auditorium of well dressed people (item no.69) (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Goon Demonstration, Dress Joint Board, Hochman, Antonini, Zimmerman, Jelo, etc. on sound truck. (P) (item no.70) (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Demonstrations against goons in dress industry, outdoor rally workers with signs. Negatives 1948. (P) (item no.71) (Box 10, Folder 72)
  (P and negatives)
- Demonstrations against goons in dress industry, outdoor rally workers with signs. Contacts (P) (item no.72) (Box 10, Folder 73)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 453 Lansdowne Avenue, Camden, New Jersey (item no.73) (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Los Angeles Joint board (Cloak) old 1948 (item no.74) (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Los Angles Cloak Joint Board New opened 1955 (item no.75) (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Dubinsky seated on park bench, reading glasses in hand, book on lap (item no.76) (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Eye Examinations (P) (item no.77) (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Eye Examinations (P) (item no.78) (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Mass Eye Examinations in shop (P) (item no.79) (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Eye Glass Examinations, optical departments (item no.80) (Box 10, Folder 81)
- Green, William at KFMV mike, 3/6/50 (item no.81), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 82)
- Cahan, Abraham at WFranklin D. Roosevelt mike, 3/6/50 (item no.82), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 83)
- Dubinsky with Austin of UN, Kahn, others at WFDR mike, Blum Memorial, 3/6/50 (item no.83), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Boston Health Center opening, 5/14/49 (item no.84), 1949 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  May 15th
- Allentown Union Health Center and Clinic Treatment, 1949 (P) (item no.85) (Box 10, Folder 86)
- New members of Local 155 receive x-ray examination as condition of membership in the union 10/15/45 (P) (item no.86), 1945 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  October 15th (P)
- Mass x-ray, demonstrated by Dr. Price in Long Island shop (item no.87) (Box 10, Folder 88)
- Local 38, mass x-ray of membership (item no.88) (Box 10, Folder 89)
- Doctors at New York Health Center looking at x-ray plates (item no.89) (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Dr. and nurse developing x-ray plates in darkroom (item no.90) (Box 10, Folder 91)
- Ear examinations (P) (item no.91) (Box 10, Folder 92)
- Mass x-rays. (P) Photographer, Harry Rubenstein (item no.92) (Box 10, Folder 93)
- X-rays, using old equipment (P) (item no.93) (Box 10, Folder 94)
- X-rays, using new modern equipment (P) (item no.94) (Box 10, Folder 95)
- David Dubinsky, Charles Zimmeman, Luigi Antonini look on as a worker is xrayed at Health Center (item no.95) (Box 10, Folder 96)
- Louis Nelson, Dr. Herbert R. Edwards (Director of the Bureau of T.B. of the New York City Department of Health) and Dr. Leo Price (item no.96) (Box 10, Folder 97)
  Watch the final examination in the mass x-ray of Local 155 members done in conjunction with the distribution of vacation checks
- International House, Israel, Building and activities (item no.97) (Box 10, Folder 98)
- Women testing out machine (item no.98) (Box 10, Folder 99)
- Hot water therapy being administered to foot of female patient (item no.99) (Box 10, Folder 100)
- Blood tests (P) (item no.100) (Box 10, Folder 101)
- Smallpox injections (P) (item no.101) (Box 10, Folder 102)
- Hayfever Department, girl receiving injection, 4/27/45 (item no.102), 1945 (Box 10, Folder 103)
- Typhus Injection, girl receiving injection (P) (item no.103) (Box 10, Folder 104)
- First Aid Station in shop, girl having finger bandaged by nurse (item no.104) (Box 10, Folder 105)
- Allergy rooms, patients being tested for allergies (item no.105) (Box 10, Folder 106)
- Flourescope examinations (item no.106) (Box 10, Folder 107)
- Taking of blood pressure (item no.107) (Box 10, Folder 108)
- General examination (item no.108) (Box 10, Folder 109)
- Electro Cardiograph treatment (item no.109) (Box 10, Folder 110)
- Drug department, modern inside only (item no.110) (Box 10, Folder 111)
- Drug departments, outside only (item no.111) (Box 10, Folder 112)
- New York Health Center information booths (item no.112) (Box 10, Folder 113)
- Dietician class for workers and nurses (item no.113) (Box 10, Folder 114)
- Early New York Health Center Interior under construction (item no.114) (Box 10, Folder 115)
- Pauline Newman, Dr. George Price- New York Health Center Christmas Party (item no.115) (Box 10, Folder 116)
- Dr. Leo Price, Rendee (druggist) and nurse look at allergy information sign on wall in corridor of New York Health Center (item no.116) (Box 10, Folder 117)
- Conference between Dr. George Price, Minkoff and worker (item no.117) (Box 10, Folder 118)
- X-ray table for legal accident case for Jimmy Lipsig (item no.118) (Box 10, Folder 119)
- Old picture of doctors at dinner, Leo and George Price and Dr. Stone (item no.119) (Box 10, Folder 120)
- Conference of nurses (item no.120) (Box 10, Folder 121)
- LaGuardia looking at x-ray equipment, Luigi Antonini, Leo Price, Pauline Newman and nurse (item no.121) (Box 10, Folder 122)
- Union Health Center staff with Dr. Leo Price (item no.122) (Box 10, Folder 123)
- Health Center European Child Adoption Committee (item no.123) (Box 10, Folder 124)
- Cilacoisis victim speaking at microphone (item no.124) (Box 10, Folder 125)
- People working in a factory (item no.125) (Box 10, Folder 126)
- Health Center Committee with Dr. Leo Price (item no.126) (Box 10, Folder 127)
- Old International Ladies Garment Health Center Committee (item no.127) (Box 10, Folder 128)
  (1 negative)
- Doctors Conference (item no.128) (Box 10, Folder 129)
- Doctor Leo Price, Union Health Center head, New York, and group of staff physicians on tour of garment shops to study work facilities, watch an operator at work (P) (item no.129) (Box 10, Folder 130)
- Union Health Center Display, Atlantic City, pics with and without Pauline Newman (item no.130) (Box 10, Folder 131)
- Nurses with x-ray equipment, no patients (item no.131) (Box 10, Folder 132)
  (2 negatives and photos)
- Heat wave diathermy (item no.132) (Box 10, Folder 133)
- Basal metabolism, nurse and patient (4P, 4N) (item no.133) (Box 10, Folder 134)
  (4P and 4 negatives)
- Two nurses prepare for worker blood pressure examination (p) (item no.134) (Box 10, Folder 135)
- Nurse attending patient on operating table (item no.135) (Box 10, Folder 136)
- Nurse demonstrating child care on baby to mother (P) (item no.136) (Box 10, Folder 137)
- New York Health Center nurses pose for picture (item no.137) (Box 10, Folder 138)
- Nurse in lab attending sterilizer (item no.138) (Box 10, Folder 139)
- Nurse in operating room, equipment shown, no patient (item no.139) (Box 10, Folder 140)
- Narrow corridor in Health Center, nurse administering heat wave treatment to patient in room at far end of corridor(P) (item no.140) (Box 10, Folder 141)
- Lab technicians working with microscope (2P, 3N) (item no.141) (Box 10, Folder 142)
  (2P and 3 negatives)
- Nurse administering short wave diathermy to woman (2P, 2N) (item no.142) (Box 10, Folder 143)
  (2P and 2 negatives)
- Doctor Leo Price consulting with worker(2P, 2N) (item no.143) (Box 10, Folder 144)
- Health Center office staffs at work (item no.144) (Box 10, Folder 145)
- New York Health Center Record Room (3P, 4N) (item no.145) (Box 10, Folder 146)
  (3P and 4 negatives)
- Registration desks, people registering, new (item no.146) (Box 10, Folder 147)
- Registration desks, people registering (3P,3N) (item no.147) (Box 10, Folder 148)
- Interview and waiting rooms, new (item no.148) (Box 10, Folder 149)
- Interview and waiting rooms (5P, 4N) (item no.149) (Box 10, Folder 150)
- Large waiting room, first floor, New York Health Center (item no.150) (Box 10, Folder 151)
  (5P and 4 negatives)
- Health Center corridor, technician waiting, seated next to table in foreground room with equipment visible at far end of corridor (item no.151) (Box 10, Folder 152)
- Health Center cafeteria, tables, woman seated (item no.152) (Box 10, Folder 153)
- Price, Georgespeaking at dinner, Mrs. Price seated (P) (item no.153) (Box 10, Folder 154)
- Lab technician examines urine specimen (2P, 1N) (item no.154) (Box 10, Folder 155)
  (2P and 1 negative)
- Nose examination, doctor nurse, and male patient (1P, 2N) (item no.155) (Box 10, Folder 156)
- Laboratory, lab technicians at work (item no.156) (Box 10, Folder 157)
- San Antonio Health Center, rented by Union (item no.157) (Box 10, Folder 158)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike-International Ladies Garment Fort (P) (item no.158) (Box 10, Folder 159)
- Kolodney and Meyers Strike- Chain gang (P) (item no.159) (Box 10, Folder 160)
- Kolodney and Meyers Strike- Children striking (P) (item no.160) (Box 10, Folder 161)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike-Bobby soxers drinking soda pop (P) (item no.161) (Box 10, Folder 162)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike- Women strikers, 2 children (boy and girl) sitting on car fender with International Ladies Garment hats and strike signs (P) (item no.162) (Box 10, Folder 163)
- Dressmakers Sympathy Strike for Kolodney-Meyers workers (P) (item no.163) (Box 10, Folder 164)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike- pickets, leaflet distribution, etc. (P) (item no.164) (Box 10, Folder 165)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike, line of women pickets reading PM (item no.1) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike, circle of women strikers in costumes (P) (item no.2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Kolodney-Meyers Strike- girls on flag bedecked truck (item no.3) (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Strikers eating at long tables, one closeup (item no.4) (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Violent strikes, beating, victims, police fights, etc. (P) (item no.5) (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Chinese Ladies Garment Workers picket sitting on step (P) (item no.6) (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Blue Bonnet Strike (P) (item no.7) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Unity House waiters striking because not rehired (P) (item no.8) (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Kay Dunhill Strike, Long Branch, New Jersey (P) (item no.9) (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Local 89 dressmakers strike in sympathy with the striking Automat workers (P) (item no.10) (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Alpena Strike (P) (item no.11) (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Local 32B Strikers pose with Charles Zimmerman (P) (item no.12) (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Local 132 pickets strike for removal of the manager, M. Feldman (P) (item no.13) (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Unusual strikes (P) (item no.14) (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Strikes on department stores (P) (item no.15) (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Artificial flower workers strike outside Macys against the selling and purchasing of non-union made artificial flowers (P) (item no.16) (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Strikers receive Strike Cards (General Strike Card) crowd around desk holding up cards (P) (item no.17) (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Heather Handkerchief Workers Strike for Union Shop (P) (item no.18) (Box 11, Folder 18)
- S & K Clothing Strike in Port Chester (P) (item no.19) (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Los Angeles California- W.R. Woodward Strike (P) (item no.20) (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Ideal Dress Corporation workers, New York, picket John Suarez, 362 5th Avenue (P) (item no.21) (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Local 142-Aritificial Flower Workers Union picket Kaplan Brothers Shop, New York (P) (item no.22) (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Strike against Puritan Dress, Berman-Levine and Samuel Blum and Sons, factory workers in Boston on strike and showroom workers in New York (P) (item no.23), 1938 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  September 1st (P)
- New York Strikes- Berger Alenick, Selmak Dress, Kaplan-Elias, Hudson Dress and Pommy Dress (P) (item no.24) (Box 11, Folder 24)
- New York Strikes- Starmaid Dress, Bellaire Garmen, Frances Dress and Marshall Dress, Blue Dale Dress, Sara Dress, Jacobs Brothers Pageant Dress and Sugarman Handwear Company (P) (item no.25) (Box 11, Folder 25)